improb.com 2019-04-08

# Privacy | Improb

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Improb, we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We are thoughtful about the personal information we ask you to provide and the personal information that we collect about you through the operation of our services.
  * We store personal information for only as long as we have a reason to keep it.
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what information on your website is shared publicly (or kept private), indexed by search engines, and permanently deleted.
  * We help protect you from overreaching government demands for your personal information.
  * We aim for full transparency on how we gather, use, and share your personal information.

Below is Improb’s privacy policy, which incorporates and clarifies these principles.

### Who We Are and What This Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy applies to information that we collect about you when you use:

improb.com

Throughout this Privacy Policy we’ll refer to our website, mobile applications and other products and services collectively as “Services.”

Below we explain how we collect, use, and share information about you, along with the choices that you have with respect to that information.

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any of our products or services that have a separate privacy policy.

### Information We Collect

We only collect information about you if we have a reason to do so–for example, to provide our Services, to communicate with you, or to make our Services better.

We collect information in three ways: if and when you provide information to us, automatically through operating our services, and from outside sources. Let’s go over the information that we collect.

####  ** _Information You Provide to Us_**

It’s probably no surprise that we collect information that you provide to us. The amount and type of information depends on the context and how we use the information. Here are some examples:

  *  **Basic Account Information:** We ask for basic information from you in order to set up your account for subscription, purchases and more.
  *  **Public Profile Information:** If you have an account with us, we collect the information that you provide for your public profile.
  *  **Transaction and Billing Information:** If you buy something from us, you will provide additional personal and payment information that is required to process the transaction and your payment, such as your name, credit card information, and contact information. **  
**
  * **Communications with Us (Hi There!):** You may also provide us information when you respond to surveys, submit your email for our newsletter subscription, or any other method to which we can contact you with.

####  ** _Information We Collect Automatically_**

We also collect some information automatically:

  *  **Log Information:** Like most online service providers, we collect information that web browsers, mobile devices, and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, IP address, unique device identifiers, language preference, referring site, the date and time of access, operating system, and mobile network information.
  *  **Usage Information:** We collect information about your usage of our Services. For example, we collect information about the actions that users perform on a site–in other words, who did what, when and to what thing on a site. We also collect information about what happens when you use our website (e.g., page views, support document searches at, button clicks) along with information about your device (e.g., mobile screen size, name of cellular network, and mobile device manufacturer). We use this information to, for example, provide our Services to you, as well as get insights on how people use our Services, so we can make our Services better.
  *  **Location Information:** We may determine the approximate location of your device from your IP address. We collect and use this information to, for example, calculate how many people visit our Services from certain geographic regions.
  *  **Information from Cookies & Other Technologies: **A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Pixel tags (also called web beacons) are small blocks of code placed on websites and e-mails. Improb uses cookies and other technologies like pixel tags to help us identify and track visitors, usage, and access preferences for our Services, as well as track and understand e-mail campaign effectiveness and to deliver targeted ads.
  *  **Order Information** : when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers [[INSERT ANY OTHER PAYMENT TYPES ACCEPTED]]), email address, and phone number.

### How We Use Information

We use information about you as mentioned above and as follows:

  * To provide our Services–Give to the best in gear, cars, clothing and more!
  * To further develop our Services–for example by adding new features that we think our users will enjoy;
  * To monitor and analyze trends of device information to better understand how users interact with our content, which helps us improve our website and make them easier to use;
  * To monitor and protect the security of our Services, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities, fight spam, and protect the rights and property of Improb and others;
  * To communicate with you about offers and promotions offered by Improb and others we think will be of interest to you, solicit your feedback, or keep you up to date on Improb and our products;
  * To personalize your experience using our Services, provide content recommendations and serve relevant advertisements.

### Sharing Information

####  _How We Share Information_

We do not sell our users’ private personal information.

We share information about you in the limited circumstances spelled out below and with appropriate safeguards on your privacy:

  *  **Subsidiaries, Employees, and Independent Contractors** **:** We may disclose information about you to our subsidiaries, our employees, and individuals who are our independent contractors that need to know the information in order to help us provide our Services or to process the information on our behalf. We require our subsidiaries, employees, and independent contractors to follow this Privacy Policy for personal information that we share with them.
  *  **Third Party Vendor** **s** **:** We may share information about you with third party vendors who need to know information about you in order to provide their services to us. This group includes vendors that help us provide our Services to you (like payment providers that process your credit and debit card information) and those that help us understand and enhance our Services (like analytics providers). We require vendors to agree to privacy commitments in order to share information with them.
  *  **As Required by Law:** We may disclose information about you in response to a subpoena, court order, or other governmental request.
  *  **To Protect Rights and Property:** We may disclose information about you when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Improb, third parties, or the public at large. For example, if we have a good faith belief that there is an imminent danger of death or serious physical injury, we may disclose information related to the emergency without delay.
  *  **Business Transfer** **s** **:** In connection with any merger, sale of company assets, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company, or in the unlikely event that Improb goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would likely be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. If any of these events were to happen, this Privacy Policy would continue to apply to your information and the party receiving your information may continue to use your information, but only consistent with this Privacy Policy.
  *  **With Your Consent:** We may share and disclose information with your consent or at your direction.
  *  **Aggregated and De-Identified Information:** We may share information that has been aggregated or reasonably de-identified, so that the information could not reasonably be used to identify you. For instance, we may publish aggregate statistics about the use of our Services.

### Security

While no online service is 100% secure, we work very hard to protect information you submit against unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction, and take reasonable measures to do so.

### Choices

You have several choices available when it comes to information about you:

  *  **Limit the Information that You Provide:** If you have an account with us, you can choose not to provide the optional account information, profile information, and transaction and billing information. Please keep in mind that if you do not provide this information, certain features of our Services–for example, paid, premium themes–may not be accessible.
  *  **Limit Access to Information On Your Mobile Device:** Your mobile device operating system should provide you with the ability to discontinue our ability to collect stored information or location information via our mobile apps. If you do so, you may not be able to use certain features.
  *  **Opt-Out of Electronic Communications:** You may opt out of receiving promotional messages from us. Just follow the instructions in those messages. If you opt out of promotional messages, we may still send you other messages, like those about your account and legal notices.
  *  **Set Your Browser to Reject Cookies:** At this time,  Improb does not respond to “do not track” signals across all of our Services. However, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies before using Improb’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Improb’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Other Things You Should Know

####  _Transferring Information_

Improb is a worldwide service. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing, transfer, and storage of information in and to the U.S. and other countries, which may have rights and protections that are different from those in your home country.

####  _Ads and Analytics Services Provided by Others_

Ads appearing on any of our Services may be delivered by advertising networks. Other parties may also provide analytics services via our Services. These ad networks and analytics providers may set tracking technologies (like cookies) to collect information about your use of our Services and across other websites and online services. These technologies allow these third parties to recognize your device to compile information about you or others who use your device. This information allows us and other companies to, among other things, analyze and track usage, determine the popularity of certain content, and deliver advertisements that may be more targeted to your interests. Please note this Privacy Policy only covers the collection of information by Improb and does not cover the collection of information by any third party advertisers or analytics providers.

####  _Advertising Privacy Statement_

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at ****hello@improb.com**  **and contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences/privacy policy link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

 **BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

###  **You can opt out of targeted advertising by:**

FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads

GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous

BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

IMPROB – Follow the instructions to unsubscribe in the email. OR Contact us here https://improb.com/contact-us/

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/.

 **DO NOT TRACK**

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

 **YOUR RIGHTS**

If you are located in certain countries, including those that fall under the scope of the European General Data Protection Regulation (AKA the “GDPR”), data protection laws give you rights with respect to your personal data, subject to any exemptions provided by the law, including the rights to:

  * Request to know personal data to which we have;
  * Request correction or deletion of your personal data;
  * Object to our use and processing of your personal data;
  * Request that we limit our use and processing of your personal data; and
  * Request portability of your personal data.

If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information here: https://improb.com/contact-us/

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Improb may change its Privacy Policy from time to time. Improb encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your consent to such change.

Update: May 23, 2018
